http://irecusa.org/privacy-policy

Independent leadership. Trusted clean energy expertise.
Other Ways to Give to IREC
Home › Interstate Renewable Energy Council (IREC) Privacy Policy
Interstate Renewable Energy Council (IREC) Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit https://irecusa.org (the “Site”). By using our Site, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Website.
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally, when you complete and submit a form on the Site, we collect certain information from you, which may include your name, title, company name, company address, email address, and phone number. Additional information may be collected as required for specific programs or events. We refer to this information as “Contact Information.”
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Contact Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Contact Information that we collect generally to fulfill any requests placed through the Site. Additionally, we use this Contact Information to:
Communicate with you;
Screen our form submissions for potential risk or fraud; and
Provide you with information relating to our activities, programs, and policies.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
IREC takes your privacy seriously. We will never sell your Personal Information. We only share your information as required by law or with trusted third-party service providers to provide you with services as described below.
We may transmit anonymized Personal Information to third party service providers to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site—you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here.
We use Pardot, LLC, a Salesforce Company, for assistance with marketing initiatives on our Website. Pardot deploys cookies for monitoring Browsing Information and allows us to collect Personal Information through forms and landing pages. Please refer to Pardot’s Privacy Policy for information on data storage and security. You can also read about how Pardot tracks web activity for details on their use of cookies.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant, or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a resident of the European Union or California, you have the right to access Personal Information we hold about you and to ask that your Personal Information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us via one of the methods listed below.
If you are a European resident note that we are processing your information to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you submit a form through the Site, we will maintain your Contact Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at info@irecusa.org or by mail or phone using the details provided below:
Interstate Renewable Energy Council (IREC)
PO Box 1156
Latham, NY 12110-1156
United States
Telephone: 1-518-621-7379
Consumer Protection
Regulatory Reform
Workforce Education
Publications
Recent News & Events
About Us
Interstate Renewable Energy Council (IREC)P.O. Box 1156Latham, New York 12110-1156518-621-7379info@irecusa.orgCopyright © 1998 – 2020Interstate Renewable Energy CouncilPrivacy Policy | Disclaimer
Name
Email address
Organization
Organization Type
--Select--
Clean Energy Company
College or Training Organization
Federal/State/Local Government
Stay up-to-date with IREC's programs and policies in clean energy!
For the next 72 hours, you can download any IREC report without having to fill out this form again! This feature
requires the use of cookies in your browser. Check your browser settings if you experience any problems.
